他是伪装大师
He's a master of disguise.
-她疯了  -认真想想 亨利
- She's gone mad. - Think about it, Henry.
他知道科兹洛娃夫人的财宝
Someone out there knows about the Kozlova fortune, right?
是所谓的财宝
Alleged fortune.
铁拳说我们不是在找犯罪团伙
Knuckles said we weren't looking for a criminal gang.
-铁拳  -因为没有团伙
- Knuckles? - Because there was no gang.
-是单独作案  -小毛毛看透了一切...
- It was one man. - Feathers knew all along...
小毛毛 谁是小毛毛
Feathers? Who's Feathers?
-报摊的鹦鹉吗  -不是...
- The parrot at the news-stand? - No...
咱们能不能正常一点
Can we just return to Planet Earth for a moment?
菲尼克斯·布坎南是个受人尊敬的一流的演员
Phoenix Buchanan is a highly respected, award-winning actor
还是白金俱乐部的会员
and a member of our Platinum Club.
-他不是小毛贼  -等等 亨利...
- He is not a petty thief. - Hang on a minute, Henry...